Don Yoder collection of tape and disc recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Sound recording, December 31, 1972 and 1973, RYQ 3230; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:15, Side B: 00:32:42): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR252)
    Old Order River Brethren New Year's Eve talk, given by Bishop John Sauder, to young people.
    Side B (1973)
    Singing. Old Order River Brethren. Lining of hymns by Deacon John Strickler, Mountville, Pennsylvania, recorded at Lancaster Mennonite School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording, 1973, RYQ 3231; 1 sound cassette (00:18:48): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR253)
    Singing. Old Order River Brethren. Lining of hymns by Deacon John Strickler, Mountville, Pennsylvania, recorded at Lancaster Mennonite School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. This cassette was sent to Don Yoder by John A. Hostetler.
    Archivist's note: for the most part the content is the same as SR252, Side B. The relevant part of the recording ends at 00:12:25; the balance is content unrelated to the collection.
    Engineer's notes: static noise and channel imbalance throughout Side A. Low level at end of content. Side B is blank.
  - Sound recording, 1978, RYQ 3232; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:28:37, Side B: 00:23:20): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo and mono (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR254)
    Interview of Fr. McGowan, St. Patrick's Church. Topics include life and death, purgatory, etc.
    Engineer's notes: Side A is stereo, Side B is mono. Extreme channel imbalance throughout Side A. Speed fluctuation closes Side A and opens and closes Side B.
  - Sound recording, November 8, 1981, RYQ 3233; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:42:26, Side B: 00:35:00): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR255)
    Pennsylvania German worship service, St. John's United Church of Christ, Coopersburg, Pennsylvania. The pastors participating in the service were Labert Altemose (Faith United Church of Christ, Grantville, Center Valley), Richard Druckenbrod (interim pastor, St. John's United Church of Christ, Coopersburg), and Richard Wolfe (pastor, St. James Lutheran Church, Coopersburg).
    SR255 and SR256 are effectively two copies of the same recording.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation ends Side B.
  - Sound recording, November 8, 1981, RYQ 3234; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:42:14, Side B: 00:34:51): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR256)
  - Sound recording, March 1983, RYQ 3235; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:13:16, Side B: 00:02:34): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR257)
    African American gospel music: Chords of Harmony, recorded by Ray Allen. Selections include "Leaning on Jesus," "Steal Away to Jesus," "In My Savior's Care," and other songs.
  - Sound recording, October 30, 1983, RYQ 3236; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:02, Side B: 00:44:29): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR258)
    African American gospel music: Western and Eastern Shore Singing and Praying Bands, Friendship M.E. [Methodist Episcopal] Church, Friendship, Delaware (Jon David, recordist). This tape is a copy.
    Engineer's note: heavy vocal distortion throughout both sides.
    Western Shore Band
    Eastern Shore Band
  - Sound recording, October 22, 1989, RYQ 3237; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:25:02, Side B: 00:40:46): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR259)
    Pennsylvania German worship. Host: United Church of Christ. Richard Druckenbrod, preacher.
    Engineer's notes: vocal distortion throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation opens Side B. Slight channel imbalance throughout Side B.
  - Sound recording, April 30, 1980, RYQ 3238; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:50, Side B: 00:29:17): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR260)
    Excerpts from the congregation and choirs of Sanctuary Church of the Open Door, 61st and Larchwood, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Portion of a sermon by Rev. Audrey F. Bronson, Pastor. Side B includes selections from the Philadelphia Mass Choir. Recorded by Becky Carlton for Don Yoder's Folk Religion class.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise and channel imbalance throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation ends Side A. Volume gradual increase to level at beginning of Side B.
  - Sound recording, 1976, RYQ 3239; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:20:45, Side B: 00:20:45): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR261)
    Engineer's notes: extreme channel imbalance throughout both sides, very low level on right channel at end of Side A. Recording stutters throughout Side B.
    Dubs of commercial music, unrelated to the collection.
    Recording made at the Second Pilgrim Baptist Church (location unconfirmed); primarily vocal music, accompanied by organ. See SR290.
  - Sound recording, 1985, RYQ 3240; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 01:00:50, Side B: 00:52:02): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR262)
    1985 Hepler reunion. One of Don Yoder's grandmothers was a Hepler family member. This is a recording of activities that took place during the reunion. Don Yoder was a speaker at one of the events.
    Engineer's notes: Channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides. Extreme low level on right channel throughout Side A, inactive on Side B.
  - Sound recording, 1985, RYQ 3241; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 01:01:00, Side B: 00:52:10): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR263)
    Hepler reunion (copy). See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's note: extreme channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, August 10-11, 1991, RYQ 3242; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:31:46, Side B: 00:07:50): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR264)
    1991 Hepler reunion tour.
    Engineer's note: channel imbalance throughout both sides. Archivist's note: the volume level becomes very low towards the end of Side B.
    Side A (August 10, 1991)
    Recording of various events during the reunion: a tour of Lehigh County (led by Don Yoder), a visit to Emmaus Moravian Church, and a visit to Zion Lehigh Lutheran Church (Lower Macungie Township)
    Side B (August 10-11, 1991)
    A visit to Zion Lehigh Lutheran Church (continued From Side A). Part of the graveside ceremony in Pitman (August 11).
  - Sound recording, May 11-12, 1993; May 24, 1993, RYQ 3243; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:03, Side B: 00:33:56): analog, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR265)
    Recording of activities during the Hepler tour 1993, tape 1 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise and channel imbalance throughout both sides. Noisy background on both sides.
    May 24 End of trip: last dinner, in Mainz (see SR272 for the first part of the dinner)
    May 11 Reichelsheim (only a small fragment was recorded successfully)
    May 12 Eberbach
    May 11 Eberbach (continued from Side A)
    May 11 Sinsheim
    May 11 Schwaigern
  - Sound recording, May 12-17, 1993, RYQ 3244; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:50, Side B: 00:45:14): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR266)
    Recording of activities during the Hepler tour, tape 2 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise and channel imbalance throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation across both sides.
    May 12 Schwaigern (continued)
    May 13 Besigheim
    May 13 Besigheim (continued); Gross-Bottwar; Steinham; Murr; Benningen; Marbach; Stuttgart
    May 16 Vaihingen; Sersheim; Horrsheim
    May 17 Vaihingen
  - Sound recording, May 16-17, 1993, RYQ 3245; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:08, Side B: 00:47:08): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR267)
    Recording of activities during the Hepler tour, tape 3 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides. Heavy distortion across Side B.
    May 16 Vaihingen; Sersheim; Horheim [sic]
    May 16 Bietigheim-Bissingen
    May 17 Vaihingen; Lomersheim; Maulbronn; Bietigheim-Bissingen (lecture in the hotel - beginning
  - Sound recording, May 17, 1993, RYQ 3246; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:58, Side B: 00:46:58): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR268)
    Recording of activities during the Hepler tour, tape 4 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise throughout both sides. Channel imbalance throughout Side A, gradual imbalance throughout Side B.
    Vaihingen (continued); Lomersheim; Maulbronn; Bietigheim-Bissingen (lecture in the hotel)
    Lecture in the hotel (continued)
  - Sound recording, May 17-20, 1993, RYQ 3247; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:42, Side B: 00:47:13): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR269)
    Recording of activities during the Hepler tour, tape 5 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides. Heavy distortion on Side B.
    May 17 Lecture in the hotel (conclusion)
    May 19 Nöttingen
    May 19 Ellmendingen
    May 20 Palatinate; London; Anweiler; Aschbach; Kaiserslautern (Roland Paul's lecture at the Institute; conclusion on SR270)
  - Sound recording, May 20-21, 1993, RYQ 3248; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:02, Side B: 00:47:01): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR270)
    Recording of activities during the Hepler tour, tape 6 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation ends Side B.
    May 20 Kaiserslautern (continued from SR269; conclusion of Roland Paul's lecture at the Institute); Steinwenden; Kaffeetrinken (afternoon coffee).
    May 20 Steinwenden (conclusion); Kaiserslautern (lecture and reading at the hotel)
    May 21 Beginning of trip to Speyer and Freinsheim
  - Sound recording, May 21-22, 1993, RYQ 3249; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:51, Side B: 00:47:05): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR271)
    Hepler tour, tape 7 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Side A (May 21)
    Speyer; Freinsheim.
    Side B (May 22)
    Western Pfalz; Farm; Schloss Lichtenberg; Grumbach.
  - Sound recording, May 22-24, 1993, RYQ 3250; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:31, Side B: 00:46:43): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR272)
    Hepler tour, tape 8 (Timothy Shipe, recordist). Don Yoder is a speaker. See notes for SR262.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise throughout both sides. Channel imbalance throughout Side A, fluctuating imbalance throughout Side B.
    May 22 Herren-Sulzbach; Tiefentaler Mühle; Unter-Jeckenbach (Pfälzer Abend)
    May 22 Unter-Jeckenbach (Pfälzer Abend, continued)
    May 24 Mainz - final dinner (conclusion is at the beginning of tape 1)
  - Sound recording, April 15, 1976, RYQ 3251; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:29:59, Side B: 00:29:59): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR273)
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance throughout Side A. Speed fluctuation opens Side B. Sharp volume dip through to end of Side B.
    Bucks County Grass [bluegrass band, recorded live], tape 1, set 1
    From the start to 00:06:06: Bucks County Grass [bluegrass band, recorded live]. From 00:06:16 to the end of the recording: a woman can be heard speaking about embroidery (?), and instructs another woman on using a loom..
  - Sound recording, April 15, 1976, RYQ 3252; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:12, Side B: 00:41:55): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR274)
    Bucks County Grass [bluegrass band, recorded live], tape 2, sets 3 and 4
    Engineer's note: fluctuating channel imbalance throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, April 16, 1986, RYQ 3253; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:33:42, Side B: 00:33:44): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR275)
    Daniel Womack in concert at the International House, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
    Archivist's note: Side B ends abruptly.
    Engineer's note: channel imbalance throughout Side B.
  - Sound recording, April 6, 1980, RYQ 3254; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:13, Side B: 00:27:31): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR276)
    Música de la capilla de la Milagrosa (Easter): songs sung in Spanish during a religious service.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation during middle of Side B drops left channel through to end.
  - Sound recording, December 1981, RYQ 3255; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:15:55, Side B: 00:14:25): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR277)
    Tunes from "Hill Country Tunes" - Maggie Holtzberg
    Archivist's note: according to Maggie Holtzberg this is probably her own recordings of these fiddle tunes, which include "The Road to Boston" and "Soldier's Joy." She was a student on one of Yoder's classes, which included a study of Pennsylvania traditions. She may have submitted a paper on Samuel Bayard.
    Engineer's notes: speed fluctuation at beginning of Side A and end of Side B. Fluctuating channel imbalance throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3256; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:12, Side B: 00:47:59): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR278)
    Don Yoder's lecture on Quaker genealogical research. Before the lecture begins he calls it "lecture number 4." Side B ends at 00:36:43.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise throughout both sides. Volume on left channel briefly dips. Left channel drops out at end of Side B.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3257; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:21, Side B: 00:12:59): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR279)
    Vanessa Merlis interviews several people on the subject of amulets.
    Engineer's notes: fluctuating channel imbalance, machine noise, and vocal distortion/robotic vocal sounds throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, February 11, 1989, RYQ 3258; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:37, Side B: 00:47:46): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR280)
    Interview of an unidentified Quaker woman (born circa 1910), conducted by Anna Morris. The woman was at Woodbrooke Study Center, a Quaker college in Birmingham, England, in the 1930s. The recording on Side B ends abruptly.
    Engineer's note: extreme channel imbalance throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, March 9, 2000, RYQ 3259; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:38, Side B: 00:09:03): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR281)
    Em Sterling Zimmerman Zi Leweslauf (Sterling Zimmerman's life story as told by himself). Recited in English.
    Engineer's note: channel imbalance and high frequency loss throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3260; 1 sound cassette (00:28:14): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR282)
    An unidentified man asks questions about butchering, ham as a traditional dish at Easter, etc. Interview subjects are Irwin Yoder (Sam Yoder's father), George Yoder (Irwin's brother), and Mr. Reppert. In Pennsylvania German and English. Recorded at Sam Yoder's "place" (probably a farm), in Shoemakersville, Pennsylvania. From the documentation: Butchering (Yoder-Schlegel-Worley).
    Engineer's notes: fluctuating channel imbalance throughout Side A. Side B is blank.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3261; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:31:10, Side B: 00:31:21): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR283)
    Country butchering on Side A, and possibly other topics on Side B; the majority in Pennsylvania German. On Side B: relevant content begins from 00:01:46 to 00:08:12, and from 00:16:01 to 00:22:49 (preceded by unrelated music). From 00:22:51 an unidentified man tells the story of David and Goliath, in English. Some opinions about folklore are included, and this version has a particularly military angle. From the documentation: Newton Bachman (Robert I. Schneider - Dr. Yoder - Folklife)
    Robert I. Schneider probably was a student in one of Yoder's classes.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance, heavy vocal distortion, high frequency loss, and speed fluctuations throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3262; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:48, Side B: 00:27:21): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR284)
    "Pennsylvania German (Dutch) Poems and Stories," by Ernie Bechtel. Recitations in Pennsylvania German.
    Archivist's notes: it is likely that Sides A and B are switched as digital files.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance throughout Side A. High frequency loss throughout Side B.
  - Sound recording, April 4, 1983, RYQ 3263; 1 sound cassette (00:36:17): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR285)
    Don Yoder delivers a talk in Pennsylvania German at the Versammling Berks County 1983, probably at Kutztown State College. Following the end of the lecture (00:20:47) other activities can be heard, including musical performances. From the documentation: Versammling: Berks County KSU. Side A: 5/6; Side B: 6/6.
    Archivist's note: A versammling is a type of assembly or social gathering. Kutztown State College became Kutztown University, later in 1983.
    Engineer's notes: fluctuating channel imbalance throughout Side A. Speed fluctuation ends Side A. Side B is blank.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3264; 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR286)
    No available documentation. The recording has not yet been digitized.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3265; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:39:47, Side B: 00:47:21): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR287)
    Content unrelated to the collection; probably includes audio recorded from radio and television programs.
    Engineer's notes: right channel inactive for majority of both sides. Channel imbalance on latter segment of Side B.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3266; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:33, Side B: 00:16:09): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR288)
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and high frequency loss throughout both sides. Left channel drastically drops off from midpoint through to end of Side A, gradually returns through to end. Speed fluctuations near end of Side B.
    From the start to 00:15:57: Don Yoder interviews a woman on the subject of healing. She identifies herself at 00:15:26 as Mrs. Beverly (the surname is not deciphered). From 00:16:00 to the end of the side (which cuts off abruptly): Don Yoder interviews an unidentified person on subjects including working charms, protection from evil, etc. Continued on Side B
    Continued from Side A. The recording ends abruptly.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3267; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:50, Side B: 00:29:24): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR289)
    Ora Watson on quilting, tape 1. Tape 2 is SR217.
    Engineer's notes: vocal distortion, channel imbalance, and tape machine noise throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, 1976, RYQ 3268; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:43:59, Side B: 00:45:39): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR290)
    Second Pilgrim Baptist Church, sides II and III. Relevant content on Side B starts at 00:01:30. See SR261.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and heavy distortion throughout both sides. Speed fluctuation ends Side A and at end of introduction of Side B. Volume dips on left channel during Side B.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3269; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:58:59, Side B: 00:58:56): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 1 channel, Type I, mono (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR291)
    First and second parts of an African American church service. See SR292 for what may be the third part of the recording.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise throughout content. High frequency loss throughout Side B.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3270; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:29:54, Side B: 00:30:16): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR292)
    Side A includes the third part of an African American church service. See SR291 for what may be the first and second parts of the recording. Side B contains dubs of commercial recordings unrelated to the collection.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides. High frequency loss across both sides. Speed fluctuation ends both sides.
  - Sound recording, 1994, RYQ 3271; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:44:41, Side B: 00:41:54): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR293)
    "Mir Lanne Deitsch," by Richard Druckenbrod (a guide to reading Pennsylvania German), tape 1
  - Sound recording, 1994, RYQ 7501; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:44:09, Side B: 00:39:49): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR294)
    "Mir Lanne Deitsch," by Richard Druckenbrod (a guide to reading Pennsylvania German), tape 2
  - Sound recording, 1994, RYQ 7502; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:42:54, Side B: 00:37:29): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR295)
    "Mir Lanne Deitsch," by Richard Druckenbrod (a guide to reading Pennsylvania German), tape 3
  - Sound recording, 1994, RYQ 7503; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:25:45, Side B: 00:20:59): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR296)
    "Mir Lanne Deitsch," by Richard Druckenbrod (a guide to reading Pennsylvania German), tape 4
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance and tape machine noise throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, circa 1960-1969, IDA 00865; on one side of 1 sound disc (lacquer on card) (00:01:16): analog; 6 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR297)
    One man interviews another man, who is speaking in Italian.
    This Voice-O-Graph disc probably was recorded no later than the 1960s. It was mailed to Don Yoder circa 1979.
  - Sound recording, December 23, 2001, RYQ 3061; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 01:00:09, Side B: 00:12:49): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR298)
    A church service (possibly Lutheran), which may have been recorded in Pullman, Washington (at one point, the city of Pullman was mentioned).
- Series 3: Graphic Materials
  - George Kaufmann, dulcimer builder and player, stringing his most recent board, September 1968, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2003/051: PH01 (Box 1/4)
  - A closer view of the "board," September 1968, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2003/051: PH02 (Box 1/4)
    The photo was taken the same day as AFC 2003/051: PH01.
  - Farm buildings (?) undated, 1 photographic negative: black and white; 3 in. x 1 1/2 in.; AFC 2003/051: PH03 (Box 1/4)
    The item looks like a double exposure
- Series 4: Moving Images